<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Petify</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">625574624349-a9gghguck7351srd92uame9tb68mq3po.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="this_is_item_sample">This is item sample!</string>

    <string name="title_intro_1">Khám Phá Ngay Hôm Nay!</string>
    <string name="content_intro_1">Nơi tình yêu dành cho thú cưng trở thành hiện thực!</string>
    <string name="title_intro_2">Khám Phá Sản Phẩm Đỉnh Cao</string>
    <string name="content_intro_2">Từ đồ chơi đến thức ăn, tất cả chỉ với vài cú chạm!</string>
    <string name="title_intro_3">Thể Hiện Tình Yêu Với Thú Cưng!</string>
    <string name="content_intro_3">Petify mang đến những sản phẩm tuyệt vời giúp thú cưng của bạn luôn vui vẻ và hạnh phúc!</string>
    <string name="tv_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="tiep_theo">Tiếp theo</string>
    <string name="bat_dau">Bắt đầu</string>
    <string name="tv_dangnhap">Đăng nhập vào tài khoản của bạn bằng email hoặc mạng xã hội</string>
    <string name="chao_mung">Chào mừng trở lại</string>
    <string name="tao_moi">Tạo tài khoản mới</string>
    <string name="tv_tai_khoan">Có vẻ như bạn không có tài khoản hoặc kết nối với mạng xã hội</string>
    <string name="chua_co_tai_khoan">Chưa có tài khoản?</string>
    <string name="dang_ky"> Đăng ký</string>
    <string name="dang_nhap">" Đăng nhập"</string>
    <string name="da_co_tai_khoan">Đã có tài khoản?</string>
    <string name="google">Google</string>
    <string name="nhap_lai_mat_khau">Nhập lại mật khẩu</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="ten">Tên</string>
    <string name="hoac">Hoặc</string>
    <string name="facebook">Facebook</string>
    <string name="quen_mat_khau"><u>Quên mật khẩu?</u></string>
    <string name="mat_khau">Mật khẩu</string>

    <string name="tv_update_pass_success">Cập nhật mật khẩu \n thành công</string>
    <string name="tv_success_pass">Mật khẩu của bạn đã được cập nhật thành công</string>

    <string name="tv_ma_xac_minh">Chúng tôi đã gửi mã xác minh đến số điện thoại di động của bạn</string>
    <string name="tv_mat_khau_mơi">Vui lòng nhập mật khẩu của bạn</string>

    <string name="tv_dat_lai_mat_khau">Chọn chi tiết liên hệ nào chúng tôi sẽ sử dụng để đặt lại mật khẩu của bạn</string>
    <string name="tiep_tuc">Tiếp tục</string>
    <string name="xac_nhan">Xác nhận</string>

    <string name="nhanh"><u>đ</u>20.000</string>
    <string name="tong_so_tien_1_san_pham"><u>đ</u>120.000</string>
    <string name="tong_tien_hang"><u>đ</u>100.000</string>
    <string name="phi_van_chuyen"><u>đ</u>20.000</string>

    <string name="tv_chinh_sach_bao_mat">Chính Sách Bảo Mật Của Petify</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy1">Chúng tôi, đội ngũ phát triển ứng dụng Petify, cam kết bảo vệ quyền riêng tư của bạn. Chính sách bảo mật này giải thích cách chúng tôi thu thập, sử dụng, chia sẻ và bảo vệ thông tin cá nhân của bạn khi sử dụng ứng dụng Petify.</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy2">Chúng tôi có thể thu thập các thông tin sau từ người dùng:</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy3">Thông tin cá nhân: Tên, địa chỉ email, số điện thoại, địa chỉ giao hàng, và thông tin thanh toán để hoàn tất đơn hàng và giao hàng.</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy4">Thông tin hoạt động: Dữ liệu về các thao tác, lịch sử mua hàng và các hành động khác trong ứng dụng để tối ưu hóa dịch vụ và hỗ trợ khách hàng.</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy5">Chúng tôi sử dụng thông tin cá nhân của bạn cho các mục đích sau:</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy6">Xử lý đơn hàng và thanh toán: Để đảm bảo quá trình mua hàng và thanh toán diễn ra an toàn và chính xác.</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy7">Cải thiện dịch vụ: Phân tích dữ liệu để nâng cao hiệu suất ứng dụng, phát triển tính năng mới, và tối ưu hóa trải nghiệm người dùng.</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy8">Gửi thông báo và khuyến mãi: Cập nhật thông tin đơn hàng, thông báo bảo trì và các ưu đãi đặc biệt cho người dùng đã đăng ký.</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy9">Chúng tôi cam kết không chia sẻ thông tin cá nhân của bạn với bên thứ ba ngoại trừ các trường hợp sau:</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy10">Các đối tác giao hàng và thanh toán: Để hoàn thành các yêu cầu đơn hàng và quá trình giao hàng.</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy11">Theo yêu cầu pháp lý: Khi có yêu cầu từ cơ quan pháp luật hoặc để bảo vệ quyền lợi của chúng tôi và người dùng.</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy12">Chúng tôi áp dụng các biện pháp bảo mật phù hợp để bảo vệ thông tin cá nhân của bạn, bao gồm:</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy13">Mã hóa dữ liệu: Các thông tin nhạy cảm như thông tin thanh toán được mã hóa để bảo vệ an toàn.</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy14">Giới hạn quyền truy cập: Chỉ nhân viên cần thiết mới có quyền truy cập vào thông tin cá nhân của người dùng.</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy15">Người dùng có các quyền sau đối với thông tin cá nhân của mình:</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy16">Quyền truy cập: Bạn có thể yêu cầu truy cập hoặc sao chép dữ liệu cá nhân mà chúng tôi lưu trữ.</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy17">Quyền chỉnh sửa: Yêu cầu chỉnh sửa nếu thông tin của bạn không chính xác hoặc không đầy đủ.</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy18">Quyền xóa bỏ: Yêu cầu xóa dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn khỏi hệ thống của chúng tôi.</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy19">Chính sách bảo mật này có thể được cập nhật theo thời gian. Chúng tôi sẽ thông báo qua email hoặc trên ứng dụng nếu có bất kỳ thay đổi quan trọng nào.</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy20">Nếu có bất kỳ câu hỏi nào liên quan đến chính sách bảo mật hoặc cách chúng tôi xử lý thông tin cá nhân, vui lòng liên hệ với chúng tôi qua:</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy_email">Email: doan379a@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="tv_pricacy_hotline">Hotline: 0123-456-789</string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="question2_card20">The Seven of Swords represents secrecy, dishonesty, or evasion. Your ex may be keeping aspects of their relationship hidden or may be involved in a relationship that lacks openness. They might be avoiding full commitment or not entirely forthcoming about their status.</string>
    <string name="question24_card20">This card represents deception and self-sabotage. Your money block may stem from a lack of trust in yourself or your financial abilities. You might be avoiding financial responsibilities or engaging in self-sabotaging behaviors due to fear of failure. To overcome this block, work on building self-confidence and recognizing your capacity to manage your finances effectively. Be honest with yourself about your financial situation and take proactive steps to improve it.</string>
    <string name="question39_card20">This card symbolizes deception, avoidance, and strategic thinking. It suggests that you might be in denial about the effects of your bad habits on your health. The Seven of Swords encourages you to be honest with yourself and face the reality of your situation. Avoiding the truth will not lead to positive change. Instead, take a proactive approach to understand how these habits might be undermining your health.</string>
    <string name="question45_card20">This card symbolizes deception, avoidance, and strategy. It suggests that you may be avoiding certain truths about your health or not facing the reality of your situation. The Seven of Swords encourages you to be honest with yourself and recognize any unhealthy behaviors you might be justifying or ignoring. Consider what aspects of your health you may be trying to sidestep or rationalize.</string>
    <string name="question18_card21">This card represents generosity and giving. To enhance your relationship with money, consider the importance of both giving and receiving. Engage in acts of kindness, such as donating or helping others financially. Cultivating a spirit of generosity can create a flow of abundance, reinforcing the idea that money is meant to circulate rather than be hoarded.</string>
    <string name="question21_card21">This card represents generosity and giving. It indicates that money may come your way through acts of kindness, whether it be from receiving help from others or engaging in charitable endeavors yourself. It encourages you to create a flow of energy in your financial life by giving and receiving. Networking or building relationships within your community may also lead to financial opportunities.</string>
    <string name="question29_card21">This card represents generosity and balance in giving and receiving. It indicates that your financial difficulties can be alleviated through support from others or by being open to assistance. You may find that seeking help or sharing resources can create a positive flow of abundance in your life. This card encourages you to both give and receive with an open heart, as this can lead to financial resolution.</string>
    <string name="question30_card21">This card represents generosity, balance, and reciprocity. It suggests that your financial support may be beneficial not only for your family but also for you, as long as there is a balance in giving and receiving. Consider whether your support is fostering a sense of responsibility and mutual aid within the family. If your assistance is leading to growth and reciprocity, it can be a positive choice to continue your support.</string>
    <string name="question52_card21">The Six of Pentacles encourages generosity and receiving support. This card suggests that reducing stress might involve accepting help from others or seeking balance in giving and receiving. Whether by delegating tasks or spending time helping someone in need, finding ways to share burdens can ease your stress.</string>
    <string name="question55_card22">The Three of Swords represents heartbreak and emotional pain. Your anxiety may stem from past traumas or unresolved feelings related to relationships or emotional wounds. This card urges you to confront these feelings and work towards healing, allowing you to release the burden they carry.</string>
    <string name="question8_card23">This card symbolizes indecision and stalemate. It indicates that you may be at a crossroads in your love life, unsure about what you truly want. You might be torn between different options or hesitant to make a decision, which can lead to prolonged periods of being single.</string>
    <string name="question22_card23">This card represents indecision and inner conflict. It suggests that you may feel torn between the desire to enjoy your money and the guilt associated with it. This inner struggle can create confusion and make it challenging to make financial decisions. Take time to reflect on what truly matters to you and how you can enjoy your money in a way that feels aligned with your values.</string>

    <string name="question23_card23">This card symbolizes indecision and inner conflict. Your financial struggles may be teaching you to make choices and take decisive action. It encourages you to confront your fears and uncertainties regarding money, allowing you to gain confidence in your financial decisions. Embrace the lesson of clarity and commit to taking steps toward financial stability.</string>
    <string name="question25_card23">This card represents indecision and inner conflict. It suggests that the one thing standing between you and success might be your inability to make clear decisions or confront important choices in your life. You may be avoiding critical issues or struggling to see the path forward. To overcome this obstacle, take time for reflection and clarity. Embrace the necessity of making choices, even if they are difficult, and trust your intuition to guide you toward the right direction.</string>
    <string name="question38_card23">This card symbolizes indecision, choices, and inner conflict. It suggests that you may be struggling with how to address your mental health trigger. The Two of Swords encourages you to confront your feelings and make a decision about how to cope. Consider seeking clarity on your emotions and avoid avoiding the issue. It may help to weigh your options carefully and choose a course of action that feels right for you.</string>
    <string name="question49_card23">This card represents indecision, inner conflict, and choices. It encourages you to confront any fears or dilemmas that may be contributing to your depression. To overcome these challenges, take the time to weigh your options and make conscious decisions about your well-being. Seeking support from friends, family, or a mental health professional can help you navigate these choices more clearly.</string>
    <string name="question17_card24">This card symbolizes feeling trapped or restricted. It suggests that someone may be thinking of you but feels helpless or unsure about expressing their feelings. They could be grappling with self-doubt or fear of vulnerability, preventing them from reaching out to you, even if they are constantly thinking about you.</string>
    <string name="question24_card24">This card symbolizes restriction and feeling trapped. Your money block may stem from limiting beliefs that make you feel powerless in your financial situation. You might be holding onto negative thoughts about your ability to create wealth or succeed financially. To break free from this block, challenge these limiting beliefs and remind yourself of your strengths and capabilities. Taking small, actionable steps can help empower you to make positive changes.</string>
    <string name="question25_card24">This card symbolizes restriction and feeling trapped. It suggests that self-limiting beliefs or fears may be the primary obstacles between you and success. You might feel paralyzed by doubt or anxiety, preventing you from taking necessary actions. To break free from this mindset, challenge those limiting beliefs and recognize that you have the power to change your circumstances. Start small and take actionable steps toward your goals to regain your confidence.</string>

    <string name="question26_card24">This card symbolizes restriction and feeling trapped. It indicates that your financial struggles may be tied to self-limiting beliefs or negative thought patterns. You might feel powerless or stuck in your current situation, preventing you from taking proactive steps to improve your finances. To address this, challenge those limiting beliefs and explore ways to empower yourself. Recognize that you have the ability to change your financial circumstances.</string>
    <string name="question27_card24">This card symbolizes restriction and feeling trapped. It indicates that your financial problems might be linked to self-imposed limitations or negative beliefs about your financial situation. You may feel paralyzed by fear or anxiety, preventing you from taking proactive steps to improve your finances. To address this, work on identifying and challenging these limiting beliefs, recognizing that you have the power to change your circumstances</string>
    <string name="question28_card24">This card symbolizes restriction and feeling trapped. It suggests that you might feel overwhelmed by your debt, believing that there’s no way out. However, this card also emphasizes that the limitations are often self-imposed. To escape this cycle, work on changing your mindset and challenge the beliefs that keep you feeling powerless. Recognizing that you have the ability to take control of your financial situation can lead to significant progress.</string>
    <string name="question45_card24">This card symbolizes restriction, feeling trapped, and self-imposed limitations. It suggests that you may feel stuck or unable to see a way out of a health issue. The Eight of Swords encourages you to recognize any limiting beliefs or fears that may be hindering your health journey. Break free from these mental constraints by seeking support or information that can help you move forward.</string>
    <string name="question55_card24">The Eight of Swords symbolizes feeling trapped or restricted by circumstances. This card indicates that your anxiety may be caused by self-imposed limitations or negative thought patterns. It encourages you to recognize that you have the power to change your situation and that you are not as confined as you may believe.</string>
    <string name="question18_card25">Embodies clarity, intellect, and authority. In the context of improving your relationship with money, this card suggests that you should approach financial matters with logic and analytical thinking. It encourages you to set clear financial goals, make informed decisions, and communicate effectively about your financial needs. By applying your rational mind to your financial situation, you can create a more balanced and healthy relationship with money.</string>

    <string name="question51_card25">Signifies the need for a strategic and disciplined approach to lifestyle changes. This card encourages you to evaluate your current habits critically and make decisions based on objective reasoning rather than emotions. It suggests that you might benefit from establishing routines that promote mental clarity and efficiency, allowing you to lead a more structured and fulfilling life.</string>
    <string name="question52_card25">Indicates that adopting a rational perspective and setting firm boundaries can help alleviate stress. This card advises you to communicate your needs clearly and make decisions that prioritize your mental well-being. Utilizing logical problem-solving skills can assist in managing stressors effectively.</string>
    <string name="question8_card26">This card represents anxiety and fear. It indicates that worries and negative thoughts may be holding you back from seeking love. You might be overthinking past failures or fearing future disappointments, leading to a self-imposed isolation that keeps you single.</string>
    <string name="question22_card26">This card represents anxiety and fear. It suggests that feelings of guilt may be tied to worries about what others think or the consequences of spending. You may be overthinking your financial decisions or experiencing guilt due to comparing yourself to others. Address these anxieties directly by reflecting on your values and reminding yourself that your financial choices are personal and valid.</string>
    <string name="question37_card26">This card symbolizes anxiety, worry, and mental anguish. It suggests that as you mature your emotional health, you may face fears or anxieties that need addressing. Acknowledge these feelings without judgment and work toward processing them. The Nine of Swords encourages you to seek support if needed and to engage in practices that alleviate stress and promote emotional resilience.</string>

    <string name="question48_card26">This card symbolizes anxiety, fear, and mental anguish. It suggests that negative thoughts or fears may be contributing to your health issues. To move forward, it’s essential to address these mental and emotional challenges. Consider seeking therapy or support groups to help process your feelings. Practicing mindfulness and self-compassion can also alleviate anxiety and create space for healing.</string>
    <string name="question55_card26">The Nine of Swords is a direct representation of anxiety and worry. This card indicates that your fears may be rooted in negative thoughts, sleepless nights, or overwhelming stress. It highlights the importance of addressing your mental state and recognizing the impact of your inner dialogue on your well-being.</string>
    <string name="question7_card27">This card often indicates curiosity and a desire for communication. It suggests that the person is interested in you but may be hesitant or unsure about how to express their feelings. They might be observing you from a distance, gathering information about you to understand their feelings better.</string>
    <string name="question25_card27">This card represents curiosity and mental agility but can also signify scattered thoughts or impulsiveness. The one thing possibly standing between you and success may be a tendency to rush into decisions without thorough consideration. You might be overwhelmed by information or distractions. To overcome this barrier, practice mindfulness and focus on developing a clear, strategic plan for your goals. Take time to think critically and evaluate your options before acting.</string>
    <string name="question43_card27">This card symbolizes curiosity, new ideas, and mental clarity. It suggests that to quit bad habits, you should remain open to learning and gaining insight. The Page of Swords encourages you to educate yourself about the impact of your habits and explore alternative behaviors. Seek out resources, support, or strategies that can guide you in your journey to break free from negative patterns.</string>
    <string name="question39_card28">This card symbolizes action, impulsiveness, and determination. It suggests that while you may be aware of your bad habits, you might need to take decisive action to change them. The Knight of Swords encourages you to be proactive and confront these habits head-on. Develop a plan to replace negative behaviors with positive ones, and commit to making those changes.</string>
    <string name="question44_card28">This card symbolizes action, ambition, and assertiveness. It suggests that you may be feeling driven and motivated to improve your health, but be cautious of rushing into things without proper planning. The Knight of Swords encourages you to channel your energy effectively and set clear, achievable health goals. Avoid impulsive decisions that could lead to burnout or injury.</string>

    <string name="question7_card29">This card reflects contemplation and evaluation. It suggests that the person is taking their time to assess their feelings towards you. They may appreciate what they see but want to ensure that it is the right time to act. This indicates a thoughtful approach to their feelings, suggesting that they do like you but may need time to fully realize their emotions.</string>
    <string name="question18_card29">This card symbolizes patience and assessment. To create a better relationship with money, take the time to evaluate your financial situation. Reflect on your investments, savings, and spending patterns. Are they aligned with your long-term goals? Cultivate patience as you work toward financial growth, understanding that progress takes time.</string>
    <string name="question30_card29">This card represents assessment and patience. It suggests that you take the time to evaluate the long-term impact of your financial support. Reflect on whether your contributions are yielding positive results for your family. If you believe that your support is fostering growth and stability, it may be worthwhile to continue. However, consider whether adjustments are needed to ensure your support leads to meaningful outcomes.</string>
    <string name="question31_card29">This card represents assessment and patience. It suggests that achieving financial security requires careful evaluation of your current situation and long-term planning. Take time to assess your financial goals, investments, and strategies. Be patient as you work toward your objectives, understanding that financial security is often built over time through consistent effort and reflection.</string>
    <string name="question34_card29">This card represents assessment, patience, and evaluation. It suggests that to speed up financial growth, you should regularly assess your progress and strategies. Take the time to review your investments and financial decisions to ensure they are aligned with your goals. The Seven of Pentacles encourages you to be patient and recognize that financial growth often takes time; however, careful planning can yield fruitful results.</string>

    <string name="question43_card29">This card symbolizes patience, assessment, and long-term planning. It suggests that quitting bad habits is a process that requires time and dedication. The Seven of Pentacles encourages you to evaluate your progress and be patient with yourself. Celebrate small victories along the way, and recognize that lasting change takes effort and commitment.</string>
    <string name="question21_card30">This card symbolizes hard work and dedication. It suggests that money may come your way through your efforts and commitment to your craft. By honing your skills and putting in the necessary work, you are likely to see financial rewards. Emphasize the importance of diligence and persistence in your endeavors to attract abundance.</string>
    <string name="question23_card30">This card embodies hard work and dedication. Your financial struggles may be teaching you the value of perseverance and the importance of honing your skills. Embrace the idea that diligence and continuous learning can lead to greater financial stability. Use this time to invest in your personal and professional development, as improving your skills may open new opportunities for income and growth.</string>
    <string name="question34_card30">This card symbolizes hard work, diligence, and skill development. It suggests that to speed up your financial growth, you should focus on honing your skills and improving your craft. Commit to continuous learning and be diligent in your efforts. The Eight of Pentacles encourages you to dedicate time and energy to your work, as consistent effort and mastery can lead to greater financial rewards.</string>
    <string name="question51_card30">This card represents hard work, skill-building, and dedication. To improve your lifestyle, consider dedicating time to developing new skills or working toward personal goals. The Eight of Pentacles encourages you to embrace a growth mindset and see life as an opportunity to improve and refine yourself. Committing to consistent practice and effort can lead to meaningful progress.</string>
    <string name="question2_card31">With the Nine of Pentacles, independence and self-sufficiency are in focus. This card hints that your ex feels empowered and comfortable being single, enjoying their autonomy and the fruits of their hard work. They’re likely cherishing this sense of freedom and are in no rush to be in a relationship.</string>
    <string name="question3_card31">This card represents self-sufficiency, independence, and comfort in solitude. Your ex may be enjoying their independence and focusing on personal achievements, feeling secure and content with the life they’re building alone.</string>
    <string name="question35_card31">This card represents self-sufficiency, financial independence, and personal achievement. It suggests that your financial situation can empower you to create the life you desire. By taking pride in your achievements and enjoying the fruits of your labor, you can cultivate a sense of abundance and fulfillment. This card encourages you to appreciate your current resources and use them to pursue your passions and goals.</string>
    <string name="question50_card31">This card represents self-sufficiency, independence, and comfort in solitude. To set healthier boundaries, focus on cultivating a sense of independence and self-sufficiency. When you feel secure within yourself, it becomes easier to protect your boundaries without fear of losing validation from others. This card encourages you to prioritize your own peace and fulfillment.</string>
    <string name="question2_card32">Representing legacy and familial stability, the Ten of Pentacles suggests that your ex might be involved in a serious relationship that feels foundational. This card implies a commitment geared toward building a future together, whether they are planning a family or focusing on a shared vision of stability and security.</string>
    <string name="question3_card32">Suggesting long-term stability, this card indicates that they might be focusing on building a secure future, whether financially or in terms of family. The Ten of Pentacles points to legacy and long-lasting contentment, emphasizing a desire for strong foundations.</string>
    <string name="question30_card32">This card symbolizes wealth, family legacy, and stability. It suggests that continuing to support your family financially can lead to a lasting legacy and create a secure foundation for future generations. The Ten of Pentacles indicates that your contributions are valued and that you are part of a larger familial support system. If your financial support fosters harmony and stability within the family, it may be worth continuing.</string>
    <string name="question31_card32">This card represents wealth, family legacy, and stability. It indicates that financial security can be achieved through building a strong foundation and planning for the future. Focus on creating long-term financial strategies, such as saving, investing, and establishing a solid financial plan. By prioritizing stability and legacy, you can work toward achieving lasting financial security.</string>
    <string name="question32_card32">This card symbolizes wealth, family legacy, and stability. It indicates that to create a life of abundance, you should focus on building a strong foundation and investing in long-term goals. This may involve nurturing your family relationships, creating a supportive community, or planning for future financial stability. By prioritizing your values and long-term aspirations, you can cultivate a life of lasting abundance.</string>
    <string name="question35_card32">This card symbolizes legacy, wealth, and long-term success. It suggests that your financial situation can help you shape your dream life by allowing you to create a solid foundation for the future. Focus on building lasting wealth that can support your goals and dreams. Consider how your financial decisions today can contribute to a legacy that reflects your values and aspirations.</string>
    <string name="question5_card33">Reflects a new venture and careful optimism. This card suggests approaching your confession with sincerity and a grounded attitude, as it may lead to something meaningful.</string>
    <string name="question21_card33">This card embodies ambition and new ventures. It indicates that money may come your way through educational pursuits or new learning opportunities. Investing in your education or developing new skills can lead to financial gain. Be open to exploring new avenues that expand your knowledge and create pathways for financial growth.</string>
    <string name="question23_card33">This card embodies ambition and new beginnings. Your financial struggles may be encouraging you to adopt a fresh perspective on money and work towards new opportunities. It teaches you to be open to learning and exploring different avenues for income. Embrace this lesson by setting realistic financial goals and being proactive in your pursuit of financial stability.</string>
    <string name="question29_card33">This card represents ambition and the pursuit of new opportunities. It suggests that your financial difficulties can be addressed by adopting a proactive approach to your finances. The Page of Pentacles encourages you to learn and explore new avenues for income or investment. Embrace your curiosity and seek out knowledge that can empower you to improve your financial situation</string>
    <string name="question32_card33">This card symbolizes ambition, exploration, and learning. It suggests that creating a life of abundance requires a willingness to learn and explore new opportunities. Stay curious and open to acquiring new skills or knowledge that can enhance your financial or personal growth. By being proactive in your pursuits and remaining open to possibilities, you can attract abundance into your life.</string>
    <string name="question33_card33">This card embodies ambition, exploration, and a willingness to learn. It suggests that manifesting your dream life requires continuous learning and growth. Be open to acquiring new skills or knowledge that can help you achieve your goals. The Page of Pentacles encourages you to take a practical approach and explore opportunities for personal and financial development.</string>
    <string name="question35_card33">This card symbolizes ambition, exploration, and a willingness to learn. It suggests that your financial situation can provide opportunities for growth and learning. By investing in yourself and acquiring new skills, you can enhance your financial prospects and create a path toward your dream life. Embrace a mindset of curiosity and exploration, as this can open doors to new possibilities.</string>
    <string name="question38_card33">This card represents ambition, curiosity, and the desire to learn. It suggests that approaching your mental health trigger with a mindset of curiosity and exploration can be beneficial. Consider seeking knowledge or resources that can help you understand and cope with your triggers. The Page of Pentacles encourages you to be proactive in your healing journey and explore different coping strategies.</string>
    <string name="question42_card33">This card represents practicality, diligence, and new opportunities. It suggests that improving your sleep may require a practical approach and a willingness to learn. The Page of Pentacles encourages you to educate yourself about sleep hygiene and practices that promote restful sleep. Explore different techniques, such as limiting screen time before bed or creating a bedtime ritual, and find what works best for you.</string>
    <string name="question44_card33">This card represents practicality, diligence, and learning. It suggests that you are in a phase of exploring new health routines or practices. The Page of Pentacles encourages you to approach your health with curiosity and a willingness to learn. Consider researching healthy habits, nutrition, or exercise programs that align with your goals and lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="question48_card33">This card represents new beginnings, practical skills, and a focus on health. It encourages you to approach your healing journey with curiosity and dedication. To move past your health issues, invest time in educating yourself about your conditions and exploring practical steps for improvement. This may involve researching healthy habits, trying new exercise routines, or adopting a balanced diet. Stay committed to your growth and learning.</string>
    <string name="question9_card34">This card embodies patience and slow progress. It suggests that meeting your soulmate may take time and require patience. They may come into your life during a period of stability or when you’re grounded and focused on long-term goals. This is a sign to trust the process, as the connection will be worth the wait.</string>
    <string name="question19_card34">This card symbolizes responsibility and perseverance. To control your spendthrift tendencies, adopt a diligent approach to your finances. Set long-term financial goals and create a plan to achieve them. Regularly review your progress and stay committed to your budget, reinforcing the habit of disciplined spending over time.</string>
    <string name="question20_card34">This card embodies responsibility and diligence. To stop overspending, adopt a disciplined approach to your finances. Establish a detailed budget that outlines your income, expenses, and savings goals. Regularly review and adjust this budget as necessary, committing to your financial plan and being accountable for your spending habits.</string>
    <string name="question25_card34">This card embodies hard work and diligence but can also indicate stagnation. The obstacle standing between you and success may be a lack of motivation or impatience. You might be putting in the effort but failing to adapt or innovate. To address this issue, assess your current strategies and be open to change. Explore new ways to approach your goals and ensure you remain flexible and proactive in your pursuits.</string>
    <string name="question34_card34">This card embodies diligence, responsibility, and practicality. It suggests that to speed up financial growth, you should take a steady and disciplined approach. Focus on creating a realistic financial plan and consistently work toward your goals. The Knight of Pentacles encourages you to be patient and thorough in your efforts, as steady progress will lead to significant results over time.</string>
    <string name="question45_card34">This card embodies diligence, responsibility, and practicality. It suggests that you may be ignoring the importance of consistent self-care and healthy routines. The Knight of Pentacles encourages you to adopt a disciplined approach to your health. Make sure you are prioritizing regular check-ups, exercise, and balanced nutrition as part of your daily life.</string>
    <string name="question47_card34">This card represents diligence, responsibility, and practicality. To feel stronger and healthier, adopt a disciplined approach to your health. Set realistic goals and create a structured plan for your physical and mental well-being. This could include meal planning, establishing a regular workout schedule, or setting aside time for mindfulness practices. Consistency and dedication will lead to long-term health improvements.</string>
    <string name="question14_card35">Practical, caring, and financially stable people, like those represented by the Queen of Pentacles, can provide grounded support and help you build a sense of stability. These individuals encourage balance, self-care, and responsibility in life.</string>
    <string name="question22_card35">This card embodies nurturing and practicality. It indicates that your guilt may stem from a sense of duty to care for others. You might prioritize the needs of family or loved ones over your own desires, leading to feelings of guilt when you choose to spend on yourself. Recognize that nurturing yourself is just as important, and finding a balance between caring for others and indulging in your own joys is vital.</string>
    <string name="question28_card35">This card embodies financial stability and nurturing. It suggests that you have the potential to cultivate a healthy relationship with money. By focusing on practicality and resourcefulness, you can develop a strategy for managing your debt effectively. This card encourages you to take charge of your finances and create a secure foundation for your financial future.</string>
    <string name="question31_card35">This card embodies nurturing and practicality in financial matters. It suggests that you can achieve financial security by adopting a nurturing approach to your resources. Focus on managing your finances wisely and being resourceful. This card encourages you to invest in yourself and your skills, as personal development can lead to increased financial opportunities.</string>
    <string name="question35_card35">This card represents nurturing, practicality, and resourcefulness. It suggests that your financial situation can support you in creating a balanced and fulfilling life. Focus on managing your resources wisely and investing in your well-being and that of your loved ones. The Queen of Pentacles encourages you to cultivate a nurturing environment that supports your dreams and allows you to thrive.</string>
    <string name="question15_card36">Representing stability, practicality, and a commitment to security, a partner like the King of Pentacles values a steady, long-term relationship. They are dependable, financially responsible, and focus on building a solid foundation for the future.</string>
    <string name="question18_card36">This card embodies financial mastery and abundance. To enhance your relationship with money, focus on cultivating qualities such as responsibility and discipline. Create a realistic budget and stick to it, emphasizing the importance of planning for the future. Embodying a mindset of abundance and confidence can help you attract wealth and create stability in your financial life.</string>
    <string name="question26_card36">This card embodies financial security and stability. It suggests that you may lack financial success due to a need for greater discipline and planning in your financial affairs. You might be neglecting long-term investments or failing to budget effectively. To address this issue, develop a comprehensive financial plan that includes saving, investing, and responsible spending. Focus on building a solid foundation for your financial future.</string>
    <string name="question27_card36">This card embodies financial security and stability. It suggests that your ongoing money problems may be tied to a need for greater discipline and long-term planning. You might be neglecting important aspects of financial management, such as budgeting, saving, or investing. To address this, develop a comprehensive financial plan that prioritizes responsible spending and saving. Focusing on building a solid foundation for your finances can help alleviate ongoing problems.</string>
    <string name="question30_card36">This card embodies financial stability, responsibility, and success. It suggests that you have the ability to support your family effectively and with confidence. The King of Pentacles encourages you to continue providing financial assistance if it leads to stability and growth for your family. Trust in your ability to manage resources wisely while nurturing your family’s needs.</string>
    <string name="question34_card36">This card symbolizes financial stability, success, and wise management. It suggests that you should approach your finances with a long-term perspective and strategic thinking. Focus on building a solid financial plan that includes savings, investments, and budgeting. The King of Pentacles encourages you to make informed decisions and consider the potential risks and rewards of your financial choices.</string>
    <string name="question51_card36">This card embodies stability, financial security, and practicality. To improve your lifestyle, pay attention to your finances and long-term goals. Consider adopting more responsible financial habits, like budgeting or saving, which can contribute to a secure foundation. The King of Pentacles also suggests valuing quality over quantity in your choices and surroundings.</string>
    <string name="question18_card37">This card symbolizes new beginnings and opportunities in the material realm. To create a better relationship with money, focus on attracting new financial opportunities. This may involve investing in your skills, pursuing new ventures, or being open to unexpected income. Emphasize a positive outlook on money as a source of abundance and growth.</string>
    <string name="question21_card37">This card symbolizes new beginnings and opportunities in the material realm. It suggests that money may come your way through a new job, investment, or project that promises financial growth. Be open to fresh opportunities and consider how you can harness your skills to create abundance. This card encourages you to take action and seize new possibilities that may present themselves.</string>
    <string name="question28_card37">This card symbolizes new beginnings and opportunities for financial growth. It suggests that there is potential for positive change regarding your debt situation. New opportunities for income or financial management could arise, allowing you to make progress. Stay open to possibilities and be proactive in seeking out ways to improve your financial situation.</string>
    <string name="question29_card37">This card symbolizes new beginnings and opportunities for financial growth. It indicates that there is potential for positive change regarding your finances. The Ace of Pentacles suggests that new ventures, job opportunities, or investments may arise, allowing you to improve your financial situation. Stay open to possibilities and be proactive in pursuing new opportunities that can lead to financial success.</string>
    <string name="question31_card37">This card symbolizes new beginnings and opportunities for financial growth. It suggests that you can achieve financial security by being open to new ventures, investments, or job opportunities. Consider exploring avenues that can lead to increased income or financial stability. Embrace the potential for abundance and take proactive steps toward building a secure financial future.</string>
    <string name="question34_card37">This card represents new opportunities, prosperity, and financial beginnings. It suggests that you should be open to new ventures or investments that can lead to financial growth. Look for fresh opportunities that align with your goals, whether it’s starting a side business, investing in stocks, or exploring new income streams. The Ace of Pentacles encourages you to take action on promising prospects to accelerate your financial journey.</string>
    <string name="question35_card37">This card represents new beginnings, opportunities, and financial potential. It suggests that your current financial situation can be a springboard for manifesting your dream life. By recognizing and seizing new opportunities for income or investment, you can lay the groundwork for your aspirations. Embrace this potential and consider how your finances can support your dreams.</string>
    <string name="question42_card37">This card embodies new beginnings, stability, and prosperity. It suggests that establishing a consistent sleep routine can lay the foundation for better sleep health. The Ace of Pentacles encourages you to invest time in creating a sleep schedule that aligns with your body\'s natural rhythms. Consistency in your sleep habits can lead to improved quality of rest and a more rejuvenated mindset.</string>
    <string name="question46_card37">This card represents new beginnings, prosperity, and potential. It encourages you to invest in your health as you would in a valuable opportunity. The Ace of Pentacles suggests considering new practices, such as trying out a new fitness regimen, exploring nutritious recipes, or investing in wellness programs. Embrace opportunities for growth and development, both physically and mentally, to cultivate a healthier lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="question21_card39">This card represents collaboration and teamwork. It indicates that money may come your way through partnerships or collaborative projects. Networking and working with others in your field can lead to new financial opportunities. Focus on building relationships that allow you to showcase your talents and skills, as this will create a pathway for monetary gain.</string>
    <string name="question18_card40">This card represents stability and security but can also indicate holding on too tightly. To improve your relationship with money, consider finding a balance between saving and spending. Reflect on whether your desire for financial security is leading to fear or scarcity mindset. Embrace the idea that money is a tool for your well-being, and practice gratitude for what you have while being open to spending wisely.</string>
    <string name="question19_card40">This card symbolizes holding on tightly to your resources. To gain control over your spending, focus on creating a budget and a savings plan that encourages financial security. While it’s essential to save, also ensure you’re not becoming overly restrictive. Find a balance that allows you to enjoy your finances while still being mindful of your spending habits.</string>
    <string name="question20_card40">This card represents control and stability but can also signify hoarding or fear of loss. To stop overspending, focus on creating a solid financial foundation. Develop a budget that prioritizes saving and essential expenses, allowing you to manage your money more effectively. Reflect on your relationship with money; ensure you’re not clinging to it out of fear, but rather using it as a tool for security and freedom.</string>
    <string name="question24_card40">This card represents holding on tightly to resources and a fear of loss. Your money block may stem from a scarcity mindset, where you believe that there is not enough to go around. This fear can lead to hoarding behaviors and an unwillingness to spend or invest in yourself. To overcome this block, work on developing an abundance mindset, reminding yourself that money can flow freely and that you can create opportunities for wealth.</string>
    <string name="question27_card40">This card represents holding onto resources and a fear of loss. It indicates that your financial problems may be related to a scarcity mindset and a reluctance to let go of control. You might be hoarding money out of fear or struggling to invest in yourself or your future. To overcome this obstacle, work on embracing a mindset of abundance. Consider taking calculated risks with your finances, as investing in yourself can lead to long-term gains.</string>
    <string name="question30_card40">This card represents holding onto resources and a fear of loss. It may indicate that you have concerns about your financial security as the breadwinner. While it’s commendable to support your family, this card encourages you to evaluate your own financial stability. Make sure that your support doesn’t jeopardize your financial health. Consider setting boundaries that protect your resources while still offering assistance.</string>
    <string name="question31_card40">This card symbolizes control over resources and the desire for security. It suggests that achieving financial security may require a careful approach to managing your finances. Focus on budgeting, saving, and being mindful of your spending habits. While it’s important to hold onto resources, ensure that you’re not overly cautious to the point of missing out on opportunities for growth.</string>
    <string name="question35_card40">This card symbolizes control, stability, and a focus on security. It suggests that your financial situation can help you shape your dream life by providing a sense of stability and security. However, it also serves as a reminder to avoid becoming overly possessive of your resources. While it\'s important to manage your finances carefully, be open to using your resources to invest in experiences and opportunities that align with your dreams.</string>
    <string name="question50_card40">This card embodies self-protection, security, and holding onto your resources. To establish stronger boundaries, protect your time, energy, and resources carefully. Avoid overextending yourself to others, and reserve your energy for those who genuinely value and respect you. This card reminds you to place a high value on your well-being and to say “no” when necessary.</string>
    <string name="question8_card41">This card often signifies feelings of lack or insecurity. It may suggest that past experiences or fears of rejection are affecting your ability to connect with others. You might be feeling unworthy of love or hesitant to open up, which can create barriers to forming new relationships.</string>
    <string name="question19_card41">This card represents feelings of lack or insecurity. It may indicate that your spending habits stem from a fear of missing out or insecurity about your financial situation. To combat this mindset, focus on gratitude for what you have. Acknowledge your achievements and practice mindfulness to help reduce the urge to overspend in an attempt to fill emotional voids.</string>
    <string name="question20_card41">This card signifies feelings of lack and insecurity. It suggests that your overspending may stem from emotional distress or the desire to fill a void. Acknowledge these feelings and address them directly. Consider exploring healthier ways to cope with stress or feelings of inadequacy that don’t involve spending. Practicing gratitude for what you have can also help shift your mindset.</string>
    <string name="question22_card41">This card represents feelings of lack and insecurity. It suggests that your guilt may stem from a fear of not having enough or worrying about your financial stability. You might have experienced financial hardship in the past, leading to an internal conflict between enjoying your money and fearing potential future scarcity. Reflect on your beliefs about abundance and work to shift your mindset toward viewing money as a source of security rather than a limited resource.</string>
    <string name="question23_card41">This card represents hardship and feelings of lack. It teaches you about empathy and understanding the struggles of others. Your financial challenges may encourage you to recognize the value of support systems, both giving and receiving help. Embrace the lesson of community and the importance of reaching out for assistance during tough times, which can foster deeper connections and support networks.</string>
    <string name="question25_card41">This card symbolizes feelings of lack and insecurity. It suggests that your fear of failure or financial instability may be a significant barrier to your success. You might be focusing too much on what you lack rather than the resources and opportunities available to you. To overcome this obstacle, shift your mindset toward abundance and recognize your strengths. Cultivating a positive outlook can help you attract the success you seek.</string>
    <string name="question26_card41">This card represents financial hardship and feelings of lack. It suggests that you may be experiencing constant financial difficulties due to a scarcity mindset or fear of not having enough. You might be focusing too much on what you lack rather than recognizing the resources available to you. To overcome this, work on shifting your perspective toward abundance and consider seeking support or community resources to improve your situation.</string>
    <string name="question27_card41">This card represents financial hardship and feelings of lack. It suggests that your ongoing struggles with money may stem from a persistent scarcity mindset. You might focus on your financial limitations rather than the opportunities available to you. This card encourages you to seek support, whether from friends, family, or financial resources, to help shift your perspective from one of lack to one of abundance.</string>
    <string name="question28_card41">This card represents financial hardship and feelings of lack. It indicates that your current situation may feel dire, but it’s essential to remember that hardships can be temporary. This card encourages you to seek support and community resources that can help alleviate your financial burden. By changing your approach to managing your finances and reaching out for help, you can create a path toward financial recovery.</string>
    <string name="question39_card41">This card symbolizes hardship, lack, and feeling isolated. It suggests that your bad habits may be leading you to experience negative consequences, such as financial strain or health issues. The Five of Pentacles encourages you to seek support and recognize that you don’t have to face these challenges alone. Consider reaching out to others for help in overcoming your habits.</string>
    <string name="question45_card41">This card represents financial and emotional hardship, feeling left out or struggling. It suggests that you might be neglecting your mental health or well-being due to external pressures, such as financial stress or feelings of isolation. The Five of Pentacles encourages you to seek support and not shy away from asking for help. Acknowledge your struggles and take steps to address them, as they can have a significant impact on your overall health.</string>
    <string name="question53_card41">The Five of Pentacles warns of financial or physical stress impacting your health. This card advises you to be mindful of any lifestyle choices that may strain your resources. Practicing good financial and health management, such as budgeting for healthcare or setting up a safety net, can give you peace of mind.</string>
    <string name="question18_card42">This card represents generosity and giving. To enhance your relationship with money, consider the importance of both giving and receiving. Engage in acts of kindness, such as donating or helping others financially. Cultivating a spirit of generosity can create a flow of abundance, reinforcing the idea that money is meant to circulate rather than be hoarded.</string>
    <string name="question21_card42">This card represents generosity and giving. It indicates that money may come your way through acts of kindness, whether it be from receiving help from others or engaging in charitable endeavors yourself. It encourages you to create a flow of energy in your financial life by giving and receiving. Networking or building relationships within your community may also lead to financial opportunities.</string>
    <string name="question29_card42">This card represents generosity and balance in giving and receiving. It indicates that your financial difficulties can be alleviated through support from others or by being open to assistance. You may find that seeking help or sharing resources can create a positive flow of abundance in your life. This card encourages you to both give and receive with an open heart, as this can lead to financial resolution.</string>
    <string name="question30_card42">This card represents generosity, balance, and reciprocity. It suggests that your financial support may be beneficial not only for your family but also for you, as long as there is a balance in giving and receiving. Consider whether your support is fostering a sense of responsibility and mutual aid within the family. If your assistance is leading to growth and reciprocity, it can be a positive choice to continue your support.</string>
    2
    <string name="question52_card42">The Six of Pentacles encourages generosity and receiving support. This card suggests that reducing stress might involve accepting help from others or seeking balance in giving and receiving. Whether by delegating tasks or spending time helping someone in need, finding ways to share burdens can ease your stress.</string>
    <string name="question15_card44">This partner is empathetic, emotionally in tune, and compassionate. They offer understanding and are deeply supportive, creating an environment where feelings are honored and nurtured.</string>
    <string name="question38_card44">This card embodies emotional intelligence, compassion, and nurturing. It suggests that being gentle with yourself is crucial when coping with mental health triggers. The Queen of Cups encourages you to prioritize self-care and engage in nurturing activities that promote emotional healing. Seek support from friends, family, or professionals who understand your journey and can provide comfort.</string>
    <string name="question36_card44">This card represents emotional intelligence, compassion, and nurturing. It suggests that you are likely in tune with your emotions, but it also encourages you to give yourself the same compassion you offer to others. The Queen of Cups reminds you to listen to your needs and take time for self-care. Prioritize your emotional health and create space for activities that bring you joy and comfort.</string>
    <string name="question37_card44">This card embodies emotional intelligence, empathy, and nurturing. It suggests that to mature your emotional health, you should cultivate a deeper understanding of your feelings and those of others. Practice self-compassion and actively nurture your emotional well-being. The Queen of Cups encourages you to connect with your emotions authentically and to create a supportive environment for yourself and those around you.</string>
    <string name="question14_card45">Individuals who are emotionally balanced, empathetic, and supportive, like the King of Cups, can help you navigate challenges with grace. These people offer wisdom and emotional maturity, allowing you to feel safe in expressing yourself and working through your emotions.</string>
    <string name="question17_card45">This card represents emotional maturity and compassion. It indicates that someone is thinking of you with deep feelings and care. They may be reflecting on their emotions towards you, possibly considering how to express their affection or support. This person likely values emotional connection and sees you as someone special in their life.</string>
    <string name="question42_card45">This card embodies emotional balance, compassion, and intuition. It suggests that to improve your relationship with sleep, you should cultivate emotional awareness and manage stress effectively. The King of Cups encourages you to practice emotional regulation and address any feelings of anxiety or unrest. Engaging in mindfulness techniques, such as meditation or deep breathing, can create a calm mind conducive to sleep.</string>
    <string name="question1_card46">Representing a new beginning filled with love and emotion, this card indicates a potential for rekindling romance. If both partners are willing to open their hearts and love again, they may find the chance for a renewed, heartfelt start together.</string>
    <string name="question4_card46">Signifies new beginnings in love and deep emotional bonds. This card suggests the potential for starting over with a fresh, more heartfelt approach.</string>
    <string name="question7_card46">This card signifies new beginnings in love and emotional connections. It indicates that the person may have a budding affection for you and is open to exploring deeper feelings. They may be ready to embrace the idea of love and connection, suggesting that their feelings could indeed be reciprocated.</string>
    <string name="question9_card46">This card represents new beginnings in love. It often suggests that you’ll meet your soulmate during a period of emotional renewal or personal growth. You may meet them when you open yourself up to love again, especially after healing from past experiences. This could happen soon if you’re in a receptive state or going through a positive transformation.</string>
    <string name="question11_card46">Symbolizes new emotional beginnings and potential love. This card indicates an openness to love and a good chance for new relationships this month.</string>
    <string name="question32_card46">This card represents emotional fulfillment, joy, and new beginnings. It suggests that creating a life of abundance starts from within. Focus on nurturing your emotional well-being and fostering positive relationships. By opening yourself to love, joy, and emotional connections, you create an abundant life filled with happiness and fulfillment. Allow your heart to guide you toward experiences that bring you joy.</string>
    <string name="question41_card46">This card embodies new beginnings, emotional fulfillment, and compassion. It suggests that healing your mind can be initiated by opening your heart to new experiences and emotions. The Ace of Cups encourages you to seek connections that foster love and support. Allow yourself to express your feelings and be vulnerable with trusted individuals, as sharing your emotions can be a powerful healing tool.</string>
    <string name="question44_card46">This card embodies emotional fulfillment, compassion, and new beginnings. It suggests that your emotional health is essential for your overall well-being. The Ace of Cups encourages you to cultivate positive relationships and express your emotions. Engage in activities that bring you joy and fulfillment, as nurturing your emotional health can significantly impact your physical health.</string>
    <string name="question49_card46">This card symbolizes new beginnings, emotional renewal, and self-love. To overcome depression, focus on nurturing your emotional health and fostering self-compassion. Engage in activities that promote self-care and emotional well-being, such as therapy, journaling, or creative expression. Opening your heart to love and connection, whether through friendships or romantic relationships, can also be a powerful source of healing.</string>
    <string name="question54_card46">The Ace of Cups suggests adding emotional openness and new connections. Allowing yourself to express love, gratitude, and kindness—whether to yourself or others—can deepen your sense of fulfillment. Opening your heart to meaningful relationships or new friendships will bring warmth and support to your life.</string>
    <string name="question1_card48">Symbolizing love and mutual respect, this card suggests a relationship that still has the potential for connection and lasting harmony. If both partners are willing to make an effort, they may successfully reconnect and work toward a stronger, stable partnership.</string>
    <string name="question2_card48">The Two of Cups symbolizes mutual attraction and emotional harmony, often seen in a balanced and committed relationship. Your ex may be involved in a new partnership that feels authentic and close, marked by trust and shared feelings. This is often a sign of a growing, promising romantic connection.</string>
    <string name="question3_card48">This card points to emotional harmony and a fulfilling relationship. If they’re not in a relationship currently, they may be open to new connections or focused on building a balanced, loving partnership when the time is right.</string>
    <string name="question4_card48">Symbolizes partnership, union, and emotional bonding. This card indicates the potential for rekindling a close relationship and sharing mutual feelings.</string>
    <string name="question5_card48">Represents mutual attraction and harmony. This card strongly encourages you to confess, as it indicates a potential for reciprocated feelings and a close connection.</string>
    <string name="question7_card48">This card represents mutual attraction and partnership. It suggests that there is a strong emotional connection between you and the other person. They likely do have feelings for you and appreciate your companionship. This card often signifies the beginning of a meaningful relationship, indicating that their feelings may be reciprocated.</string>
    <string name="question11_card48">Symbolizes a mutual attraction and partnership. This card supports the likelihood of finding a genuine connection this month.</string>
    <string name="question12_card48">The Two of Cups signals harmony, mutual respect, and partnership, suggesting you may have at least two soulmates, possibly both romantic and platonic. It highlights connections that feel like “kindred spirits,” people who understand and support you in unique ways.</string>
    <string name="question16_card48">This card represents mutual attraction, deep partnership, and emotional harmony. It’s a sign of a balanced, respectful, and loving relationship, indicating soulmate potential.</string>
    <string name="question30_card48">This card symbolizes partnership and mutual support. It indicates that your financial contributions can strengthen the bonds within your family. The Two of Cups encourages open communication and collaboration. Consider discussing financial responsibilities with your family members to ensure that everyone feels valued and involved in the support process. If your assistance fosters healthy relationships, continuing your support can be beneficial.</string>
    <string name="question35_card48">This card represents partnerships, harmony, and mutual support. It suggests that your financial situation can help you shape your dream life through collaboration and building meaningful relationships. Consider how financial partnerships or collaborations can enhance your journey. Focus on nurturing connections with others who share your vision and values, as these relationships can provide support and opportunities.</string>
    <string name="question37_card48">This card represents partnerships, harmony, and mutual support. It suggests that building healthy relationships is vital for your emotional growth. Surround yourself with supportive individuals who understand and value your emotional journey. The Two of Cups encourages you to foster connections based on trust and empathy, as these relationships can provide emotional nourishment and strength.</string>
    <string name="question46_card48">This card symbolizes partnership, connection, and mutual support. It encourages you to nurture relationships that promote your health and well-being. The Two of Cups suggests seeking out supportive friends, family members, or communities that align with your health goals. Engage in activities that foster connection, such as group exercises, wellness workshops, or simply sharing meals with loved ones. Collaborating with others can enhance your motivation and accountability.</string>
    <string name="question2_card50">With the Four of Cups, signals disinterest in current romantic options, even if new connections are available. They may feel emotionally disconnected from the idea of dating, possibly overlooking potential partners around them. This card suggests that they might be closed off to the idea of romance at present.</string>
    <string name="question3_card50">Your ex may feel some dissatisfaction or lack of excitement with their current situation. The Four of Cups suggests they might be focused on missed opportunities or unable to appreciate what’s in front of them, potentially feeling a sense of discontent or stagnation.</string>
    <string name="question8_card50">This card represents contemplation and apathy. It indicates that you may be feeling discontent or uninterested in the romantic options available to you. You might be waiting for something more fulfilling, leading to a sense of dissatisfaction with your current situation. This can keep you single if you’re not actively seeking connections that resonate with you.</string>
    <string name="question39_card50">This card represents apathy, contemplation, and discontent. It suggests that you may be feeling unfulfilled or dissatisfied with your current state due to your bad habits. The Four of Cups encourages you to reflect on what truly brings you happiness and fulfillment. Recognize how your habits may be preventing you from experiencing a more vibrant and healthy life.</string>
    <string name="question45_card50">This card represents contemplation, apathy, and reevaluation. It suggests that you might be disengaged from your health and well-being, possibly feeling dissatisfied or disillusioned. The Four of Cups encourages you to examine what you may be overlooking in your life. Take time to reflect on your emotional and physical health; you might be ignoring signs of burnout, fatigue, or emotional distress that need your attention.</string>
    <string name="question49_card50">This card represents contemplation, reevaluation, and feeling stagnant. It suggests that you may be disconnected from the opportunities around you. To overcome depression, take time to reflect on what you truly want and what makes you happy. It may be beneficial to explore new interests or rekindle old passions. Be open to receiving support and inspiration from others, even if it feels challenging.</string>
    <string name="question1_card51">This card represents loss and regret. One or both partners may still be mourning past mistakes, which can make moving forward challenging. Healing may take time, and recovery won’t come easily, but acknowledging this pain can help both find closure or a path toward reconciliation.</string>
    <string name="question24_card51">This card symbolizes loss and disappointment. Your money block might be related to past financial failures or regrets that are hindering your ability to move forward. You may be focusing too much on what you have lost rather than recognizing the opportunities still available to you. Shift your perspective to focus on the potential for growth and healing, allowing yourself to learn from the past without being held back by it.</string>
    <string name="question36_card51">This card represents loss, disappointment, and focusing on the negative. It suggests that you may be neglecting self-love due to dwelling on past mistakes or regrets. The Five of Cups encourages you to shift your focus from what’s lacking to what’s available. Recognize the positive aspects of your life and practice gratitude. Acknowledging the good can help you foster self-love and acceptance.</string>
    <string name="question38_card51">This card symbolizes loss, disappointment, and focusing on the negative. It suggests that when dealing with your mental health trigger, it’s easy to become consumed by feelings of grief or regret. The Five of Cups encourages you to acknowledge your feelings but also to recognize the positive aspects of your life. Shift your focus to what you can learn from the experience and the support that surrounds you.</string>
    <string name="question48_card51">This card represents loss, regret, and focusing on the negative. It suggests that you may be dwelling on past health challenges or losses, which can hinder your progress. To move forward, it’s crucial to acknowledge your feelings but also to shift your focus to what remains. Identify the support systems, opportunities, or lessons learned from your experiences. Practicing gratitude can help you see the positive aspects of your journey.</string>
    <string name="question55_card51">The Five of Cups signifies feelings of loss and disappointment. Your anxiety could be rooted in focusing on what has gone wrong or what you lack rather than recognizing the opportunities and positive aspects still available to you. This card encourages a shift in focus toward gratitude and healing.</string>
    <string name="question4_card52">Nostalgia and happy memories are key with this card. It often appears when past relationships are rekindled, symbolizing the possibility of reconnecting with old love.</string>
    <string name="question12_card52">Often connected with nostalgia and past-life connections, the Six of Cups indicates soulmates from both past and present. It suggests that you may feel drawn to people who seem familiar, as if you’ve known them before. These soulmates bring a sense of comfort and familiarity, indicating connections that feel destined, possibly crossing over from previous lifetimes.</string>
    <string name="question16_card52">This card often suggests a karmic connection, sometimes a soulmate from a past life or a deep emotional bond that feels familiar and comforting.</string>
    <string name="question17_card52">This card represents nostalgia and fond memories. It suggests that someone from your past is likely thinking of you. They may be reminiscing about good times you shared together, feeling sentimental about your connection. This person could be an old friend or someone with whom you have shared significant experiences.</string>
    <string name="question22_card52">This card represents nostalgia and childhood memories. It suggests that your guilt may be linked to how money was perceived in your upbringing. If you grew up in an environment where enjoying money was frowned upon, these beliefs could linger in your subconscious. Explore your past and consider how your upbringing influences your current feelings about money and enjoyment.</string>
    <string name="question32_card52">This card represents nostalgia, joy, and giving. It suggests that to create a life of abundance, you should reconnect with your inner child and embrace joy in simple pleasures. Consider ways to give back to others, as acts of kindness and generosity can attract abundance into your life. By nurturing joyful experiences and cultivating a spirit of giving, you create a life filled with richness and fulfillment.</string>
    <string name="question41_card52">This card symbolizes nostalgia, childhood memories, and emotional healing. It suggests that to heal your mind, it may be beneficial to reconnect with your inner child and explore past experiences that shaped you. The Six of Cups encourages you to reflect on joyful memories and consider how they can inform your healing journey. Engaging in activities that bring you comfort and happiness can foster a sense of emotional renewal.</string>
    <string name="question2_card53">The Seven of Cups suggests options, confusion, or even daydreaming about possibilities without commitment. Your ex may be encountering various romantic options but is uncertain about settling down, carefully weighing choices or indulging in possibilities without making any concrete moves.</string>
    <string name="question6_card53">Your admirer may be someone with many options and big dreams. They might feel overwhelmed by possibilities and not have a clear idea of what they truly want, leading to uncertainty in expressing their feelings. This card suggests they are on a journey of self-discovery and might need time to figure out their emotions before approaching you.</string>
    <string name="question17_card53">This card signifies choices and illusions. It suggests that someone is thinking of you while contemplating different possibilities in their life. They may be daydreaming about you and the potential of your connection, but they might also feel overwhelmed by the choices available to them, leading to indecision about how to approach you.</string>
    <string name="question19_card53">This card signifies choices and illusions. It suggests that you may be overwhelmed by options, leading to impulsive purchases. To control your spending, practice discernment by narrowing down your choices and focusing on what truly matters to you. Create a list of priorities before making purchases, allowing you to separate wants from needs.</string>
    <string name="question20_card53">This card symbolizes choices and temptation. It indicates that you might be overwhelmed by options, leading to impulsive purchases. To combat this, practice mindfulness when shopping. Create a list of what you need before you go out or shop online, and stick to it. Reflect on each potential purchase, asking yourself if it aligns with your values and needs.</string>
    <string name="question25_card53">This card represents choices and illusions. It indicates that confusion or unrealistic expectations may be the barrier to your success. You might be overwhelmed by options or distracted by dreams that do not align with your reality. To overcome this challenge, focus on setting clear, attainable goals and prioritizing what truly matters. Distinguish between fantasy and reality, and choose a few meaningful paths to pursue rather than spreading yourself too thin.</string>
    <string name="question26_card53">This card represents choices and illusions. It suggests that confusion or unrealistic expectations regarding your finances may be contributing to your lack of money. You might be overwhelmed by options or distracted by desires that do not align with your financial goals. To improve your situation, focus on setting clear, attainable financial objectives. Distinguish between fantasy and reality, and prioritize what truly matters to you.</string>
    <string name="question27_card53">This card represents choices and illusions. It suggests that confusion or unrealistic expectations about money might be contributing to your ongoing financial problems. You may feel overwhelmed by options or distracted by desires that don’t align with your financial goals. To address this issue, focus on setting clear, attainable financial objectives. Distinguish between fantasy and reality, and prioritize what is truly important to you.</string>
    <string name="question37_card53">This card symbolizes choices, fantasies, and the need for clarity. It suggests that as you move forward, you may encounter many emotional options and possibilities. Take the time to evaluate these choices carefully and ensure they align with your emotional health goals. The Seven of Cups encourages you to focus on what truly matters to you and avoid getting lost in illusions or distractions.</string>
    <string name="question42_card53">This card represents choices, imagination, and daydreaming. It suggests that distractions or overwhelming thoughts may be hindering your ability to sleep well. The Seven of Cups encourages you to clarify your priorities and focus on what truly matters. Consider setting aside time during the day to address any lingering worries or decisions, allowing your mind to be clear and more at ease when it\'s time to sleep.</string>
    <string name="question9_card54">This card represents leaving something behind to seek fulfillment. It suggests that you might meet your soulmate after a period of letting go of the past or leaving behind situations that no longer serve you. This encounter could happen once you’ve embarked on a journey to find deeper purpose or emotional satisfaction in life.</string>
    <string name="question38_card54">This card represents emotional withdrawal, seeking deeper meaning, and leaving behind what no longer serves you. It suggests that to cope with your mental health trigger, you may need to let go of unhealthy habits or relationships that exacerbate your distress. The Eight of Cups encourages you to seek fulfillment and prioritize your emotional well-being. It’s a call to explore new paths that promote healing and self-discovery.</string>
    <string name="question43_card54">This card symbolizes leaving behind what no longer serves you and seeking deeper fulfillment. It suggests that quitting bad habits requires a willingness to walk away from unproductive behaviors. The Eight of Cups encourages you to assess your habits and identify which ones you need to let go of. Embrace the idea of seeking a more meaningful and fulfilling life, and take actionable steps toward change.</string>
    <string name="question48_card54">This card embodies the idea of moving on and seeking deeper fulfillment. It encourages you to leave behind what no longer serves you. To move past your health issues, assess your current habits, relationships, or situations that may be contributing to your challenges. Be willing to let go of toxic influences or unhealthy routines and seek new paths that align with your health goals.</string>
    <string name="question50_card54">This card signifies walking away, letting go, and seeking fulfillment. To set boundaries, be willing to leave behind situations or relationships that no longer serve you. If people consistently disregard your limits, consider distancing yourself from these interactions. The Eight of Cups encourages you to prioritize your well-being by releasing anything that depletes your energy.</string>
    <string name="question54_card55">Represents the importance of prioritizing personal fulfillment and pursuing passions that bring you joy. It encourages you to incorporate experiences or activities that genuinely satisfy you, leading to a more enriching and fulfilling life.</string>
    <string name="question2_card56">The Ten of Cups reflects happiness, stability, and a sense of emotional completeness. If this card shows up, it suggests that your ex is likely in a fulfilling, stable relationship, possibly with long-term prospects. They may feel truly at home with their current partner, experiencing lasting happiness and harmony.</string>
    <string name="question3_card56">This card represents fulfillment and happiness, often within a family or close community. They may be focusing on emotional stability, feeling surrounded by support and love, or seeking this ideal vision of happiness and contentment.</string>
    <string name="question9_card56">This card is about harmony and fulfillment in relationships. It suggests that you may meet your soulmate when you’re feeling emotionally content and surrounded by supportive relationships. This could be during a family gathering, social event, or when you’re feeling a strong sense of belonging and happiness in your current environment.</string>
    <string name="question16_card56">A card of long-term happiness, fulfillment, and emotional harmony. It suggests that this relationship brings peace, stability, and joy, qualities of a lasting soulmate bond.</string>
    <string name="question18_card56">This card signifies fulfillment and harmony. To create a better relationship with money, reflect on how your financial goals align with your overall happiness and values. Consider what truly brings you joy and fulfillment, and evaluate your spending habits accordingly. Focus on investing in experiences and relationships that enhance your well-being rather than material possessions.</string>
    <string name="question21_card56">This card symbolizes emotional fulfillment and harmony. It suggests that money may come your way through family or community support. Consider your relationships and how they may contribute to your financial well-being. This could also indicate that creating a harmonious environment in your personal life will attract more abundance.</string>
    <string name="question34_card56">This card represents harmony, fulfillment, and emotional wealth. It suggests that financial growth is not just about material wealth; it also involves finding fulfillment in your pursuits. To speed up financial growth, align your financial goals with your personal values and what brings you joy. The Ten of Cups encourages you to create a balanced approach to finances that nurtures your overall well-being and happiness.</string>
    <string name="question40_card56">This card symbolizes emotional fulfillment, harmony, and family connections. It suggests that finding happiness may involve nurturing your relationships with loved ones. The Ten of Cups encourages you to invest time and energy into the connections that bring you joy. Seek support from your family and friends, and create shared experiences that foster love and unity. Emotional fulfillment often stems from strong, supportive relationships.</string>
    <string name="question46_card56">This card embodies emotional fulfillment, harmony, and happiness. It suggests that focusing on your emotional well-being is crucial for overall health. The Ten of Cups encourages you to create a supportive environment and foster positive relationships. Engage in activities that bring joy and fulfillment, such as spending time with loved ones or pursuing hobbies that ignite your passion. Emotional satisfaction directly influences physical health.</string>
    <string name="question47_card56">This card represents emotional fulfillment, harmony, and happiness. To improve your strength and health, focus on nurturing your relationships and creating a supportive environment. Spend quality time with loved ones, engage in meaningful conversations, and foster connections that uplift you. Emotional satisfaction plays a crucial role in physical health, so prioritize joy and harmony in your life.</string>
    <string name="question6_card57">This card represents sensitivity and creativity. Your admirer could be a younger person with an artistic soul or a romantic disposition. They may approach love with a gentle touch, expressing their feelings in subtle ways but lacking the confidence to reveal their affection directly. They might enjoy sending you sweet messages or small gifts to show they care.</string>
    <string name="question11_card57">Represents romance and gentle communication. This card suggests an innocent or unexpected love interest may appear.</string>
    <string name="question45_card57">This card embodies creativity, intuition, and emotional awareness. It suggests that you may be ignoring your emotional health or creative needs. The Page of Cups encourages you to reconnect with your feelings and explore outlets for emotional expression. Nurturing your emotional well-being through creative activities, such as art, writing, or mindfulness, can positively impact your physical health.</string>
    <string name="question47_card57">This card embodies creativity, emotional awareness, and exploration. To enhance your strength and health, connect with your emotions and engage in activities that bring you joy. Explore creative outlets such as art, writing, or music that allow you to express yourself and process your feelings. Nurturing your emotional well-being will contribute to your overall sense of strength and vitality.</string>
    <string name="question5_card58">A card of determination and confidence. This suggests that with courage and focus, going for it could lead to success in love.</string>
    <string name="question8_card58">This card symbolizes determination and willpower. It suggests that you may be focused on personal goals or ambitions, which could be taking precedence over romantic relationships.</string>
    <string name="question15_card58">This card represents a determined, ambitious, and forward-thinking partner. They are focused on growth and overcoming challenges together, motivating you to reach goals as a team.</string>
    <string name="question23_card58">This card symbolizes determination and willpower. Your financial struggles may be teaching you to harness your inner strength and focus on your goals.</string>
    <string name="question29_card58">This card represents determination and willpower. It suggests that your financial difficulties can be solved through focused effort and strategic action.</string>
    <string name="question31_card58">This card represents determination and willpower. It suggests that achieving financial security requires focused effort and strategic action.</string>
    <string name="question34_card58">This card embodies determination, willpower, and success through focused action. It suggests that to speed up financial growth, you need to take control of your financial situation.</string>
    <string name="question35_card58">This card embodies determination, willpower, and success through focused action. It suggests that your financial situation can be a driving force in shaping your dream life.</string>
    <string name="question40_card58">This card represents determination, willpower, and control. It suggests that finding happiness may require you to take charge of your life.</string>
    <string name="question43_card58">This card represents determination, willpower, and overcoming obstacles. It suggests that quitting your bad habits will require focused effort.</string>
    <string name="question46_card58">This card embodies determination, willpower, and the ability to overcome obstacles. It suggests that you should take charge of your health by setting clear goals.</string>
    <string name="question48_card58">This card represents determination, willpower, and the ability to overcome obstacles. To move past your health issues, harness your inner strength.</string>
    <string name="question10_card59">This card represents resilience and courage. Your friends likely view you as someone strong and dependable.</string>
    <string name="question15_card59">A partner with inner strength, patience, and resilience brings a sense of calm and support to the relationship.</string>
    <string name="question19_card59">This card represents inner strength and self-control. To manage your spending impulses, focus on building self-discipline.</string>
    <string name="question20_card59">This card represents inner strength and self-control. To stop overspending, focus on building your willpower and discipline.</string>
    <string name="question25_card59">This card represents inner strength and courage. It suggests that the obstacle standing between you and success may be your own self-doubt.</string>
    <string name="question26_card59">This card represents inner strength and courage. It suggests that your financial struggles may stem from a lack of confidence.</string>
    <string name="question30_card59">This card symbolizes inner strength and resilience. It suggests that you possess the capacity to support your family.</string>
    <string name="question31_card59">This card embodies inner strength and resilience. It suggests that you have the capacity to achieve financial security.</string>
    <string name="question32_card59">This card embodies resilience, courage, and self-confidence. It suggests that creating a life of abundance requires inner strength.</string>
    <string name="question33_card59">This card symbolizes inner strength, courage, and determination. It suggests that manifesting your dream life requires resilience.</string>
    <string name="question36_card59">This card embodies courage, resilience, and self-acceptance. It suggests that self-love requires inner strength.</string>
    <string name="question38_card59">This card represents courage, resilience, and self-acceptance. It suggests that to cope with your mental health trigger, you must cultivate inner strength.</string>
    <string name="question42_card59">This card symbolizes courage, resilience, and inner strength. It suggests that improving your relationship with sleep may involve overcoming challenges.</string>
    <string name="question43_card59">This card symbolizes inner strength, courage, and resilience. It suggests that quitting bad habits will require determination.</string>
    <string name="question44_card59">This card symbolizes inner strength, courage, and physical vitality. It suggests that your current health is generally strong.</string>
    <string name="question47_card59">This card symbolizes inner strength, courage, and physical vitality. To feel stronger and healthier, focus on building your physical fitness.</string>
    <string name="question49_card59">This card embodies inner strength, courage, and resilience. To overcome depression, tap into your inner resources.</string>
    <string name="question52_card59">The Strength card reminds you of the inner resilience and patience within yourself.</string>
    <string name="question54_card59">Strength highlights the need for resilience and inner courage. Adding a routine that builds physical and mental strength can empower you.</string>
    <string name="question2_card60">The Hermit often suggests solitude and introspection. If this card appears, it indicates that your ex is spending significant time alone.</string>
    <string name="question3_card60">Your ex may currently be going through a period of introspection and solitude.</string>
    <string name="question6_card60">This card indicates an introverted person who enjoys spending time alone for reflection.</string>
    <string name="question8_card60">This card signifies introspection and solitude. It suggests that you may be in a phase of self-reflection.</string>
    <string name="question13_card60">This card suggests that you may find your soulmate during moments of introspection.</string>
    <string name="question23_card60">This card symbolizes introspection and self-discovery. Your financial struggles may be prompting you to take a step back.</string>
    <string name="question29_card60">This card symbolizes introspection and seeking inner guidance. It suggests that addressing your financial difficulties may require reflection.</string>
    <string name="question31_card60">This card represents introspection and seeking inner guidance. It suggests that achieving financial security may require self-reflection.</string>
    <string name="question35_card60">This card represents introspection, inner guidance, and self-reflection. It suggests that your financial situation can help shape your dream life.</string>
    <string name="question36_card60">This card represents introspection, solitude, and inner guidance. It suggests that you may need to take time for self-reflection.</string>
    <string name="question37_card60">This card represents introspection, solitude, and inner guidance. It suggests that taking time for self-reflection is essential for maturing your emotional health.</string>
    <string name="question40_card60">This card symbolizes introspection, solitude, and inner guidance. It suggests that to find happiness, you may need to take time for self-reflection.</string>
    <string name="question41_card60">This card embodies introspection, solitude, and inner guidance. It suggests that to heal your mind, you may need to spend time alone in self-reflection.</string>
    <string name="question42_card60">This card represents introspection, solitude, and self-discovery. It suggests that improving your relationship with sleep may require some self-reflection.</string>
    <string name="question44_card60">This card embodies introspection, solitude, and inner guidance. It suggests that you may need to reflect on your health and wellness.</string>
    <string name="question46_card60">This card symbolizes introspection, solitude, and inner guidance. It suggests that you should take time for self-reflection.</string>
    <string name="question47_card60">This card symbolizes introspection, solitude, and inner guidance. To feel stronger and healthier, take time for self-reflection.</string>
    <string name="question49_card60">This card symbolizes introspection, solitude, and inner guidance. To overcome depression, consider spending time in reflection.</string>
    <string name="question52_card60">The Hermit emphasizes the importance of solitude and self-reflection. To reduce stress, this card advises you to spend time alone.</string>
    <string name="question54_card60">The Hermit suggests adding solitude or quiet time to your routine. A period of introspection can help you reconnect with yourself.</string>

    <string name="danh_gia_san_pham"> Đánh giá sản phẩm này<font color="#FF0000">*</font></string>
    <string name="th_m">Thêm</string>
    <string name="mua_ngay">Mua Ngay</string>
    <string name="c_th_b_n_c_ng_th_ch">Có thể bạn cũng thích</string>
    <string name="n_i_dung_m_t">Nội dung Mô tả</string>
    <string name="m_t">Mô tả</string>
    <string name="ch">chó</string>
    <string name="lo_i_th_th_c_ng">Loại thú thú cưng:</string>
    <string name="chi_ti_t">Chi tiết</string>
    <string name="gi_i_thi_u_v_s_n_ph_m_n_y">Giới thiệu về sản phẩm này</string>
    <string name="xem_th_m">Xem thêm</string>
    <string name="nh_gi_c_a_kh_ch_h_ng">Đánh giá của khách hàng</string>
    <string name="b_n_12">Đã bán 12</string>
    <string name="nh_nh_a_cho_ch_m_o_c_a_s_t_paw_pet_house">Nhà nhựa cho chó mèo cửa sắt PAW Pet House...</string>
    <string name="_210_000">210.000đ</string>
    <string name="t_m_ki_m_s_n_ph_m">Tìm kiếm sản phẩm</string>
    <string name="trung_t_m_tr_gi_p">Trung tâm trợ giúp</string>
    <string name="li_n_h_v_i_ch_ng_t_i_qua_mail">Liên hệ với chúng tôi qua mail:</string>
    <string name="_26_ng_38_p_y_n_l_ng_l_ng_h_ng_a_h_n_i">26 Ng. 38 P. Yên Lãng, Láng Hạ, Đống Đa, Hà Nội</string>
    <string name="xem_trong_b_n"><![CDATA[Xem trong bản đồ >]]></string>
    <string name="chat_ai">Chat Ai</string>
    <string name="please_wait">Please wait</string>
    <string name="b_t_u_cu_c_tr_chuy_n">Bắt đầu cuộc trò chuyện</string>
    <string name="_900g">900g</string>
    <string name="h_t_dinh_d_ng_himalayasssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss">Hạt dinh dưỡng himalayasssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss</string>
    <string name="_150_000">150.000</string>
    <string name="_5">5</string>
    <string name="mua_h_ng">Mua hàng</string>
    <string name="t_ng_thanh_to_n">Tổng thanh toán:</string>
    <string name="l_ch_s_n_h_ng">Lịch sử đơn hàng</string>
    <string name="h_s_c_a_b_n">Hồ sơ của bạn</string>
    <string name="ai_t_v_n">AI tư vấn</string>
    <string name="li_n_h_v_i_ch_ng_t_i">Liên hệ với chúng tôi</string>
    <string name="ch_nh_s_ch_b_o_m_t">Chính sách bảo mật</string>
    <string name="m_i_b_n_b">Mời bạn bè</string>
    <string name="th_ng_b_o">Thông báo</string>
    <string name="i_m_t_kh_u">Đổi mật khẩu</string>
    <string name="ng_xu_t">Đăng xuất</string>
    <string name="chat">Chat</string>

</resources>